<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>askinner.dev</title>
    <link>https://askinner.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on askinner.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 21:45:49 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://askinner.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes Week 4</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/20/weeknotes-week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 21:45:49 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/20/weeknotes-week-4/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a big week this week. After 3.5 years as Chief Data Officer for Meat and Livestock Australia, I have decided to leave. I have lots of emotions, sadness, excitement and pure terror. Now I have to focus on getting project Terrigal finalised.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a week of torrential rain here in New South Wales, I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything like it. It has rained solidly all week. There&amp;rsquo;s so much water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On noticing things. </title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/16/on-noticing-things./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:46:53 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/16/on-noticing-things./</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t notice things very much anymore. It might be age or routine but I don&amp;rsquo;t notice myself noting things like I used to. I don&amp;rsquo;t see things like I used to.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this is a bad thing? Maybe my mind is full and I need a break for things to perculate, to settle down and to lay the sediment lines of my mind. The downside is that life feels autonomous, like I am on a pre-determined track of routine that I need to derail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes Week 3</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/12/weeknotes-week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 06:27:42 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/12/weeknotes-week-3/</guid>
      <description>Tired. Soooo tired. I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the office in Sydney a few times this week to start to get myself back into the swing of what work used to be like. To be honest, i&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I used to do it. Getting up before five and commuting for 4 hours a day isn&amp;rsquo;t fun but it could be worse. The downside is that I am a bit tired and grumpy by the time Friday comes around - it doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that yesterday I got home to find that my two new Silkie chickens had figured out a way to get out of the hen house (i&amp;rsquo;m still not 100% sure how they did it) and are now missing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes Week 2</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/05/weeknotes-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 20:27:42 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/05/weeknotes-week-2/</guid>
      <description>Project Terrigal is continuing at pace. This week I had a few more meetings and realised that I really need to start getting my act together. It’s all getting a bit real.
I attended an advisory group for regenerative agriculture. Such a fascinating topic and so much money is being sunk into sustainability at the moment. Lots to get my head around in the carbon credits space.
Speaking of space, SpaceX had another successfulish test of the their starship this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I calculate my carbon savings</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/01/how-i-calculate-my-carbon-savings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 21:52:54 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/03/01/how-i-calculate-my-carbon-savings/</guid>
      <description>I thought that I would write a few words about how I calculate the Co2 emissions that I post to Twitter each day.
On my property I have 32 Tindo Solar panels producing 15kWh of energy from the sun. Each day after the sun has gone down, I sum what has been generated and post it to Twitter along with an estimate of how much Co2 it has saved from my daily carbon footprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeknotes Week 1</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/02/26/weeknotes-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 15:07:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/02/26/weeknotes-week-1/</guid>
      <description>New blog new rhythm, new me so I thought I’d have a stab at weeknotes.
This week I went back to work after a few days off. I’m starting up a new personal project - we’ll call it terrigal. It’s going to be a big deal for me so I started making some phone calls. I’ve also had a few other ideas for small experiments in food and fibre that I’m going to make a start on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another test</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/snippet/another-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:01:13 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/snippet/another-test/</guid>
      <description>This is another test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test snippet</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/snippet/test-snippet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 23:55:18 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/snippet/test-snippet/</guid>
      <description>This is a test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/2021/01/21/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 14:27:12 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/2021/01/21/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>hello</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://askinner.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askinner.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Andrew Skinner. I am a Brit Australian living somewhere on the beautiful NSW Central Coast. I am a Software Engineer, data geek and maker of things. I have been doing these things for quite a long time. I specialise getting technology into challenging environments (and yes, that can also include offices, people&amp;rsquo;s living rooms and into web browsers). As such, I lead teams of talented digital experts inventing and delivering new software products and services across industries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
